vivyxprinting.com 2012-12-30

# Poster Printing and Large Format Prints Cheap!

## Orders, Returns & Guarantee

Order at VivyxPrinting.com with confidence! We guarantee a high quality print. If you are not satisfied for any reason, simply let us know within 5 days of receiving your print and we will offer a re-print at no additional charge. 

### Fast Turnaround

Vivyx Printing ships orders as quickly as possible. Standard Processing orders ship no later than 5 business days from the day after your order was placed. That means you will receive your print in 6-10 business days of when your order was placed. Standard USPS Priority Mail is the default shipping option at checkout. This service may take up to 10 days to deliver. 

**Standard Processing time is up to 5 business days following the day when the order is placed. For faster processing, select Expedited Processing during checkout.** Expedited Processing ensures your order will ship by the end of the next business day. 

### Pre-Ship Visual Inspection

Your print is visually inspected by our quality control department before it is shipped, to ensure you receive a high-quality print. This is a manual process, not performed by machines. We believe in delivering quality! 

### Special Quality Notice

During the photo upload and configuration process, you may be alerted that your uploaded photo is not big enough to produce a very high quality print in the size you have selected. You will be given an option to select a smaller size, or proceed anyway. If you choose to proceed anyway, accepting that your print may be of reduced quality, VivyxPrinting.com does not guarantee the quality of the resulting print and will not refund or reprint the order! 

### How to Request a Reprint or Refund

If your print quality is not satisfactory, or is defective, you may request a reprint or refund by contacting us or calling Customer Service between 10am-6pm MST (Monday-Friday.) 

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

When creating an account or placing an order with us, you may provide certain information as requested in the applicable forms. We then use that information as necessary to process your order or complete other requests you may make via our website. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. This information does not identify you or any customer, rather it is general information about percentage of visitors that use particular features on our website. 

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your assigned account using the password provided. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Security Policy

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Our checkout process uses industry standard SSL encryption of all communication between your computer and our servers. 

Our servers utilize all reasonable security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information, and your credit card information is encrypted on our servers. 

Our team members are carefully vetted before hiring to ensure that they do not pose a risk to your private information, and their access to your data is limited to only what they need in order to perform their job functions. 

## SPAM Policy

We are committed to strict anti-SPAM policies. You will only receive emails from us as a result of specific site interaction (such as placing an order). You will only receive our newsletter if you have specifically requested to receive it, and you may opt-out at any time. 

Further, as part of our privacy policy, we do not subscribe you to third party newsletters or share our subscriber database with any third party.
